{
    "subject": "resource/Eric_Feldt",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathYear",
    "object": "1968",
    "human_readable": "Eric Feldt died in 1968.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8606016039848328,
            "question": "When did Eric Feldt die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7217785716056824,
            "question": "How old was Eric Feldt when he died?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6954289674758911,
            "question": "Was Eric Feldt alive in the year 1969?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6263542175292969,
            "question": "What was the cause of Eric Feldt's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5025334358215332,
            "question": "What year was Eric Feldt born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36058005690574646,
            "question": "Where did Eric Feldt live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3186286687850952,
            "question": "Are there any significant events associated with Eric Feldt's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3094903528690338,
            "question": "Who were some of Eric Feldt's contemporaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30489659309387207,
            "question": "What field was Eric Feldt known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28602832555770874,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Eric Feldt?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Feldt died in 1968.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4059_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field was Eric Feldt known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4059_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some of Eric Feldt's contemporaries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4059_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any significant events associated with Eric Feldt's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4059_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4059_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4059_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4059_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4059_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4059_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4059_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4059_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4059_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4059_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4059_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple, i.e., Eric Feldt indeed died in 1968. The context information confirms this fact with a mention of his date of death as 1968."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe document states that Eric Augustus Feldt's date of death is 1968, which matches the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}